kbr.com 2019-08-06

# Privacy Policy | KBR

Thank you for your trust in KBR and for taking the time to read our Privacy Statement. KBR is a global provider of differentiated professional services and technologies across the asset and program lifecycle within the Government Solutions and Energy sectors with operations in 40 countries. This Privacy Statement is provided to let you know how we protect the privacy of personal information provided to us in connection with your use of this website.

## Purpose of This Privacy Statement

This Privacy Statement explains what KBR does with personal information provided to us through this Site, such as your name, mailing address or email address. It explains in general terms how we collect, use, share, store and safeguard that information, as well as our reasons for collecting it through this website. It also contains information on how to contact us to exercise rights that you have in relation to your personal data (as defined by your country’s laws), as well as how to contact us if you have a question or concern.

## EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Website Privacy Statement

As further described in  _[KBR's Privacy Shield Notice](https://kbr.com/sites/default/files/2019-06/KBR%20Privacy%20Shield%20Notice_1.pdf)_ , KBR, Inc., and KBRwyle, have certified to and comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of human resource personal information transferred from the European Union and/or European Economic Area to the United States. The Privacy Shield principles to which they adhere for that personal data are: Notice; Choice (Consent); Accountability for Onward Transfer; Security; Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation; Access; and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit  _[www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/)_.

## Collection of Your Information

Much of our website does not require any form of registration or identification. However, some functions of our website may require registration, such as those that necessarily require us to identify you in order to answer a question that you may ask. It is up to you to choose whether you want to register for any programs through our site which may be available to the general public (such as investor relations webcasts). It may not be possible for you to gain access to certain parts of the site that are restricted to certain registered users. If you register for a KBR program or service, or otherwise provide personal information to us through this website, KBR limits the collection of your personal information to that which is appropriate and proportionate for the intended use.  This may include, for example, your name, contact details, and other personal information relevant to the purpose for which you are visiting our website. We also  offer you the option to discontinue your consent ("opting out" or "unsubscribing") if you later decide that you no longer want to participate in the program or service.

## Collection of Anonymous Computer Information /“Cookies”

Like virtually all websites, this website collects anonymous information known as “cookies” if your computer is set to allow that type of collection. “Cookies” are small pieces of data sent from a website and stored on a website user's web browser while a user is browsing a website.  (You can turn off the ability to collect some of this information on most computers, and can learn more about how to do so, as well as the types of ‘cookies’ that we collect, by clicking on our Cookies Notice.) As further explained in our Cookies Notice, the use of cookies does not harm your computer or directly identify individuals.  Rather, their use allows us to evaluate how our website performs and to monitor traffic to the site. (For those who are interested in the details, some of the typical computer techniques we may use are "cookies", "internet tags" which are also called "action tags", "single-pixel GIFs", clear GIFs, "invisible GIFs, and "1-by-1 GIFs). If you would like more information about web tags and cookies associated with on-line advertising or how to opt-out of third-party collection of information, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative website, an independent website not sponsored by or affiliated with KBR.

## Sharing Your Information with Third-Parties

KBR does not sell or share your personal information with unaffiliated third-parties, such as marketers, for their own separate use. When you provide personal information to us through our website, it may be accessible to some of our business partners, such as companies we retain to fulfil requests for information, or provide assistance to us on specific programs or projects. We require third-party business partners to protect personal information in accordance with applicable laws and in a way that is consistent with KBR’s standards. We also obtain written assurances from them that they will not use your personal information for any separate use or allow other third parties that they may retain to do so.

There may also be instances where we may be required to share your information with third-parties who are not our business partners, such as in connection with fulfilling our legal or compliance obligations. Please note that most entities receiving personally identifiable information under these conditions (e.g., courts, the police, other law enforcement agencies) have legal obligations under the privacy and security laws to protect your information.

Personal Information collected from you may also be transferred to a third party in the event that a part of your business (or this website) is sold, assigned or transferred. If so, we would require the buyer, assignee or transferee to treat your information in accordance with this Privacy Statement.

## Sharing Your Information with Other KBR Companies

The information that you provide to us may sometimes be shared with other KBR companies (subsidiaries and affiliates within the KBR global group.) If so, and regardless of the KBR company or its location, we require that they uphold a similar level of protection for your data as that described in this Privacy Statement.

## Security and Protection of Your Information

We use appropriate technical, administrative and physical safeguards to protect data that pertains to you from loss, misuse, alteration, destruction or unauthorized access.  We update these safeguards to address new threats and changes in the legal requirements. At the same time, you should recognize that no organization can guarantee the absolute security of personal information.

## Transfer of Your Information

KBR is a global company.  As such, your personal data may be transferred outside of the country where you reside.  If you live outside of the U.S., you should know that the data privacy laws vary from one country to another, and may not provide the same level of protection as those in your home country.  Nevertheless, KBR has adopted measures to ensure that the personal data entrusted to us via this website is adequately protected irrespective of where it is accessible or stored.

## Protection of Children

This website is not intended for use by minors and our business (including our website) is not the type that would naturally attract the attention or interest of minors. We comply with the laws of the U.S. and other countries that protect the privacy of children.

## Use of Your Information for Marketing

Personal Information collected through this website may be used for marketing-related purposed where we have provided notice and obtained consent from the individual to do so, or where otherwise permitted by applicable laws.  Individuals always have the right to withdraw consent (opt-out) of the use of their personal information for a marketing-related purpose, and can do so by using the Contact Us link on this website, or contacting us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#40032f2e342123341533002b22326e232f2d).

## Accessing Your Information

To the extent that KBR holds any identifiable information about individuals that was collected through this website, we comply with applicable laws relating to access and alteration of that data. All requests to update or access your information will be subject to verification of the identity of the requesting individual.

## Information for E.U. Residents

If you are a resident of the European Union or European Economic Area, you should know that KBR upholds the following rights of individuals:  The right to be informed about the collection and processing of your data; the right to access your data; the right to rectification; the right to erasure/right to be forgotten; the right to object to direct marketing, including profiling; the right to withdraw consent for data processing activities based on consent; the right to object to processing based on legitimate interests; the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority; the right to data portability, and the right to deactivate non-essential Cookies.  To exercise these rights, you may contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#8fcce0e1fbeeecfbdafccfe4edfda1ece0e2). Please note that we may require proof of your identity and full details of your request before we process your requests. Please also note that some of these rights are limited, and that KBR will apply them in accordance with applicable E.U. laws.

## Retention of Your Information

KBR retains personal information provided to us via this website in accordance with business and legal needs, and then securely destroys that information.  In some situations, we may choose to remove the personal identifiers or archive the data so that it is no longer processed or accessible.

## Updates to this Privacy Statement

We may update this Privacy Statement from time to time. If we do so, we apply any changes that we make to personal information that we collect after the changes are posted.

## Links to Other Websites

This Privacy Statement applies only to this website and not to any other websites that may be linked to our site. Since we are unable to control the Internet or the websites of other companies, we cannot be responsible for the standards of websites other than our own. This Privacy Policy is not intended to be linked to any non-KBR website.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Statement, please write to us at: KBR Inc., Attention: Data Privacy Lead, 601 Jefferson, Houston, Texas USA 77002, or email us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#6a2905041e0b091e3f192a01081844090507).
